Matthew Angel

Web Developer

For the past three years I have been involved in various projects that involve web development, artist management, and music production. As I continue to navigate through my career and teach myself new technologies, I yearn to become a member of a team that can benefit from my skillset and assist me in continuing to build on my knowledge.

23matthewangel@gmail.com

Miami

github.com/mattangelmia

3057739645

in linkedin.com/in/matt-angel1

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp (400+ Hours) IronhackMiami

08/2020 - 10/2020

Bachelor of English, Editing, Writing, and

Florida State University, Tallahassee, FL

08/2015 - 12/2017

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer eMed Digital Healthcare

08/2021 - Present Miami, Fl

eMed is democratizing healthcare with a digital point-of-care platform that provides fast, easy and affordable at-home healthcare testing.

Achievements/Tasks

- Collaborated with Designers to turn mockups/wireframes into fully functioning web pages.
- Successfully coded a full website overhaul for emed.com that has over a million visitors a month(new header, footer, overall contents on all web pages.
- Built landing pages for clients using Hubspot modules consisting of HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Built databases within the Hubspot platform and used javascript and HubL (Hubspot syntax) to request the data and render it on different web pages.
- Fixed bugs from existing webpages to enhance the overall user experience.

SKILLS



PROJECTS

eMed.com

 Homepage of eMed Digital Healthcare, a healthcare based tech startup out of Miami, Fl

DevLink

- Technologies Used: HTMl, CSS, Javascript, React.js, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDb, Boostrap
- Social media website specifically made for coders looking to collaborate and get feedback on their projects
- Live Demo:https://dev-link.netlify.app/

Ergheist Battle Tactics

- Technologies Used: HTMl, CSS, Javascript, Canvas.js
- Virtual tabletop style JavaScript-based game where each character has different ranges of attack and damage
- Live Demo: https://xenodochial-nightingale-702408.netlify.app/

Portfolio Website

- Technologies Used: HTMl, CSS, Javascript
- Webpage designed to introduce myself and display my works
- Live demo: https://mattangelmia.github.io/portfolio/

The New Normal

- Technologies Used: HTMl, CSS, Javascript, React.js
- A news style React app that has current information on topics ranging from weather to flight information. Used axios to fetch api
- Live Demo: https://the-new-normal-informative.netlify.app/

CheckMate

- Technologies Used: HTMl, CSS, Javascript, React.js, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDb
- To-do list app for different shopping occasions
- Live Demo: https://checkmatelist.herokuapp.com/

LANGUAGES

Fnalish Full Professional Proficiency Spanish Full Professional Proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Redline Media Group

12/2020 - Present

Dania

Achievements/Tasks

- Code responsive emails using HTML CSS and Javascript.
- Create user interfaces, using front-end languages.
- Develop email marketing campaigns.
- Work closely with creative team to decide on best practices for email designs.
- Manage and organize assets for all email campaigns (300+ monthly).
- Analyze and resolve bugs that arise in coding process.

Front End Developer (Contract Role)

NinjaRMM, LLC

11/2020 - Present Achievements/Tasks

- Maintain and improve company website
- Use a variety of programming languages to create userfriendly web pages
- Work as part of a multidisciplinary team with other professionals; such as, back-end developers and web designers
- Designing and managing the website back-end including database and server integration

Artist Management (Contract Role)

Miami Crooner

11/2018 - 05/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed contacts with relevant individuals and organizations
- Scheduled the client's performances
- Established artist awareness through social media platforms
- Managed business and financial affairs for artist; such as, arranging travel, managing social media, and recruiting bands
- Designed promotional material such as flyers, rate cards, posters, signage, testimonials and event materials